[♪♪♪]
[Boy speaks indistinctly]
Boy: Ha! Ha!
[Speaks in foreign language]
[Yelling indistinctly]
Come, come!
Please! Please! Please!
[♪♪♪]
[Whispering] Aziz. Aziz.
Aziz, light!
Aziz, light.
We start again.
"When the three planets are in eclipse,
the black hole, like a door, is opened.
Evil comes...
Spreading terror and chaos."
See the snake, Billy? The ultimate evil.
- Make sure you get the snake.
- Yes, I've got your snakes.
I got all the snakes.
So when is this snake act
supposed to occur?
Huh? Well, if this is the five...
And this is the one...
[Whispering indistinctly]
Every 5000 years.
So I've got some time, then.
[Snoring]
[Gasps]
Ah, you bring them water.
Good boy. I will take it to them.
Go with god. Be safe from evil.
Pacoli: You see here these
different peoples, or symbols of people...
Gathering together the four elements
of life: Water, fire, earth, air...
Around a fifth one.
A fifth...
Element.
Forgive me, lord.
They already know too much.
[Glass clinks]
Ah, father.
- Yes, how are you today?
- Well, Billy. You have some glasses?
- Of course.
- Father, I'm so glad to see you.
It's the most extraordinary thing.
I mean, look,
it's the greatest find in history.
Yes. You must be parched.
Huh? Oh, yes, yes. I'm sorry.
I mean, it's like a battle plan.
Here, the good. Here, the evil.
And here, a weapon against evil.
I'm going to be famous.
Then... then let us...
Let us toast to your fame.
Oh, yes. To fame.
Salute.
You can't drink a toast with water.
Billy, in my sack, the grappa.
[Men yelling nearby]
[♪♪♪]
[Groans]
This I don't understand. But this...
This could be something...
Prehistoric.
Maybe. I don't know.
But wait.
Here. Here.
[Children laughing nearby]
Boy: Look, look.
They're here.
Pacoli: This man...
This perfect being.
I know this is the key. I know it.
This divine light they talk about.
What is divine light?
Aziz, light!
Much better. Thank you, Aziz.
My lord.
[Mouthing]
[Growling]
Father, this is the most unbelievable thing
I have ever seen.
Don't you think...?
[Stammering]
Are you German?
Lord, I know he was about
to discover everything.
But there is no worry.
I was there in time.
Mondoshawan:
Priest, you and those before you...
Have served us well.
But war is coming.
Stones not safe on earth anymore.
Is really amazing.
[Growling and snorting]
[♪♪♪]
The fifth element.
Take the stones.
My lord...
If you take the weapon, we will be
defenseless when evil returns.
In 300 years, when evil returns...
So shall we.
Oh, professor.
Professor.
[Stammering]
Don't move!
-I have a gun! Priest: Billy.
Please, understand. They are our friends.
Fflends?
Father, they've killed the professor!
They're monsters!
I'll explain everything. Billy.
- You're with them?
- Billy, look at me.
Look at me. I am your friend.
- No, father.
- Billy, look at me!
Please, put the gun down.
Billy, no!
[Mon doshawan groans]
[Rumbling]
Hurry! The wall is closing!
Mondoshawan:
Here is your mission now:
Pass your knowledge to the next priest
as it was passed on to you.
I will do as you command,
but, please, hurry, you still have time.
Mondoshawan: Time not important.
Only life important.
[♪♪♪]
I will fulfill my mission!
You can count on me!
I will pass the knowledge
until your return!
Man 1:
Deploy inter-ship stabilizers.
Man 2: Power capacitors, check.
Man 3: Base modulation nominal.
[Indistinct chatter]
- Anything yet?
- No, sir.
- Not even a temperature?
- The thermo-analyzers have jammed.
One of them shows a million degrees,
the others minus 5000.
Let's see it.
[Controls beeping]
It's taking shape.
Send out a probe.
Man: Ladies and gentlemen,
the president of the federated territories.
On air with general staedert
in 30 seconds.
[Gasps]
Oh, I saved this seat for you, father.
- President on the line, sir.
- We're in position, Mr. President.
I have to address the supreme council
in 10 minutes. Just the facts, general.
There are no results from the chemical
and molecular analysis as yet.
All the calibers are overshot.
We 're initiating
a thermonucleatic imaging.
So, what you're saying is,
you don't know what this is.
Not yet, sir. All we know is,
it just keeps getting bigger.
Recommendation?
My philosophy, Mr. President,
is shoot first and ask questions later.
I don't like uninvited guests.
- All right, then, staedert...
- Cornelius: Mr. President?
Yes?
Computer: Priest vito Cornelius,
expert of astrophenomenon.
I have a different theory
to offer you, sir.
You have 20 seconds.
[♪♪♪]
Imagine for a moment that this...
Thing is not anything
that can be identified...
Because it prefers not to be.
Wherever there is life,
it brings death...
- Because it is evil. Absolute evil.
- One more reason to shoot first.
Evil begets evil, Mr. President.
Shooting will only make it stronger.
[Probe beeping]
Probe will obtain its objective
in five seconds.
Growth rate is at 27 percent.
Your theory is interesting,
but we don't have time to go into that now.
Time is of no importance, Mr. President.
Only life is important.
You're right.
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
We're gonna protect the life
of some 200 billion of my fellow citizens.
General, you may fire when ready.
Up-front loading of a 120-zr missile.
Marker lights on the objective.
Its structure has just solidified
on the surface.
I think it's anticipating the attack.
Anticipation denotes intelligence.
The most terrible intelligence imaginable,
Mr. President.
The ship is in combat formation.
Missiles are loaded, Mr. President.
-Staedert. Staedert: Yes, sir.
- I have a doubt.
- I don't, Mr. President.
What happened?
Staedert, can you hear me?
Staedert? What happened, staedert?
- Did you destroy it?
- I'm about to, sir.
The planet has increased
in diameter by 200 percent.
It's moving towards the ship.
What...? What do we have
that's bigger than 240?
Nothing, sir.
Staedert, do you hear me?
Get out of there.
I don't want an incident.
Do you hear me, staedert?
Get out of there.
Can you hear me, staedert?
Do you understand? Listen.
This is the president.
That's an order.
Do you understand me?
Do you hear me?
[Breaking up on radio]
Get out of there! Answer me!
[Yells]
[Groaning]
[♪♪♪]
Computer: Four a day.
[Meowing]
I'm trying.
Computer: To quit is my goal.
[Phone ringing]
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm up.
All right, I'm up.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes?
Man [on phone]:
Hey, dog brain, finger here.
- Hi, sweetie.
- I love you too, major...
But you haven't called me that
since basic training.
- I was talking to the cat.
- Oh, yeah, I forgot...
You still prefer your cat
to the real thing.
Korben:
At least the cat comes back.
You still pining for that two-timing slut?
There are a million women out there.
I don't want a million women.
I just want one.
The perfect one.
- It don't exist, major.
- Yeah, I know. Ugh.
- What?
- Just found a picture of you.
- Oh, how do ilook?
- Like shit.
Must be an old picture.
Listen, you gotta bring me your hack
for a six-month overhaul.
- Negative.
- Asap.
I don't need one.
Hey, you forgetting who sat next to you
for 1000 missions? I know how you drive.
Finger, I drive a cab now,
not a space fighter.
Okay, so tell me. How many points
you got left on your license?
Major, how many points?
- At least 50.
- Heh-heh.
Know what?
You gotta learn how to lie better.
See you tonight.
Female voice:
Welcome to paradise.
Man [on TV]:
Welcome to fhloston paradise.
It's Ruby rhod, your main man,
and I will tell you live at 5...
The name of the winner of the
super-green gemini croquette contest!
The winner will go with me
for two days to fhloston paradise.
So tune in to radio cosmos.
Don't watch it all day, sweetie.
It'll rot your brain.
For a perfect world.
- Give me the cash.
- Been here long?
Yeah, long enough.
Come on, give me the cash.
Is that a z-140? Alleviated titanium.
- Neurocharged assault model.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Hm. Good thing for me it's not loaded.
[Laughing]
- What do you mean, it's not loaded?
- Well, you have to...
You have to push
that little yellow button to load it.
[Laughs nervously]
Take your time.
Oh, god.
You want me to...?
Okay.
[Gun cocks]
- There you go.
- Aah!
Give me the cash!
[Gun whirs]
Man:
That's a very dangerous gun.
You know, maybe you better let me
hang on to this one for you, huh?
- You don't mind, do you?
- No.
- You sure?
- No. Take it. I don't need it.
[♪♪♪]
[Speaks indistinctly]
That's a very nice hat.
You like it? Ungh!
God!
Computer:
Please enter your license.
Yes, yes, just a minute.
Welcome on board, Mr. Dallas.
Good morning. Sleep well?
Yeah, me too.
- I had a horrible nightmare.
- Propulsion 2x4.
You have five points left
on your license.
Yeah, thank you for reminding me.
Have a nice day.
Why not?
[Car horns honking]
You have 48 hours.
That's the length of time it needs
to adapt itself to our living conditions.
- And then?
- And then it will be too late.
The goal of this thing is not
to fight over money or power...
But to exterminate life.
All forms of life.
So what you're telling me, father,
there's nothing that can stop this.
There is only one thing.
Cornelius: The mondoshawan have
the only weapon to defeat evil.
Four elements...
Gathered around a fifth...
Supreme being, the ultimate warrior,
created to protect life.
Together they produce what
the ancients called the light of creation.
Able to bring life to the farthest reaches
of the universe.
But if evil stands there...
Then what?
Then light turns to dark.
Life to death...
Forever.
Sir, there's a mondoshawan spaceship
at the frontier...
Requesting permission
to enter our territory.
President: Give it permission to enter
our territory with my warmest regards.
Thank you.
Man [on radio]:
Permission to enter granted.
[♪♪♪]
[Computer beeping]
We are lost.
Mangalore:
Aknot, we are connected to earth.
[Growls]
[Comm beeping]
Mr. Zorg's office.
Aknot [on comm]: It's aknot,
Zorg:
I'm so glad to hear you, aknot.
The mission is accomplished.
You'll have what you asked for
in a few hours.
Good. I'll meet you at my factory.
The attack was launched
by two unregistered warships.
Close all borders and declare
a state of general alert.
Yes, sir.
Try to make contact
with the mondoshawans.
- We owe them an explanation.
- Sir.
Three hundred years of waiting
for nothing.
Father,
you should go home now and rest.
The mondoshawan...
I am their contact on earth.
They will come for me.
Father, this is government business now.
I will keep you informed.
[♪♪♪]
The rescue team has reported
from the mondoshawan crash site.
Any survivors?
Only one.
Munro:
That what you call a survivor?
A few cells are still alive.
It's more than I need.
- Have you identified it?
- We tried...
But the computer went off the charts.
You see, normal human beings
have 40 DNA memo groups...
Which is more than enough
for any species to perpetuate itself.
This has 200,000 memo groups.
- Sounds like a freak of nature to me.
- Yeah, can't wait to meet him.
You okay, general? Over here.
Excuse me.
Okay, general,
I want to show you something here.
This is a normal human DNA chain, okay?
You, me, anybody, right?
Watch this.
The compositional elements
of his DNA chain are the same as ours.
There's more of them, tightly packed,
with infinite genetic knowledge.
Almost like this being was engineered.
- Is there any danger?
- No, no, no.
We put it through
the cellular hygiene detector.
The cell is, for lack of a better word...
Perfect.
Okay, go ahead.
But Mr. Perfect better be polite.
Othen/vise, I turn him into cat food.
Activate it.
[♪♪♪]
Tissue processing.
Ten seconds to ultraviolet protection.
Mactilburgh:
This is the last phase.
The cells are bombarded
by greasy solar atoms...
Which forces the body
to react to protect itself.
That means growing skin.
Wonderful.
Reconstruction complete.
Remove the shield.
I told you. Perfect.
Thermal bandages.
I'd, um, like to take a few pictures...
For the archives.
[Gasps]
[Grunting]
[Growls]
[Panting]
[Speaking in divine language]
- What's she saying?
- I don't know.
Activate the phonic detector.
Heh.
Is, uh...? Is that thing solid?
- Unbreakable.
- Good.
If you want out...
You're going to have to learn
to develop those communication skills.
[Breathing heavily]
[Growling]
[Grunts]
General alert.
[Alarm wailing]
[Man speaking indistinctly]
[♪♪♪]
Perfect.
[Alarm buzzing]
Two men with me.
The rest in the main ventilation.
Okay, sir.
This way.
Officer 1:
Okay, lady, stay calm.
This is the police.
There's nowhere else to go.
So you're gonna slowly turn around
and put your hands on the floor.
Do you understand me?
She doesn't.
[Gasps]
I think we need a flying unit here.
Officer 2 [on loudspeaker]:
This is the police. This is the police.
We are processing your identification.
Please put your arms up
and follow our instructions.
She has no file.
[Police siren blaring]
[Korben yells]
Computer:
You just had an accident.
Yes, I know I just had an accident,
you daffy bastard!
- You have one point left on your license.
- You have one point...
Look out!
No, no! Left!
I can't believe it. Shit.
[Grunts]
Any survivors?
[♪♪♪]
You okay?
[Chuckles]
[Speaking in divine language]
Boom.
Boom. Yeah, I understand "boom."
Bada boom.
Big. Big bada boom.
Big...
Bada big boom.
- Yeah, big bada boom.
- Bada boom.
Big boom. Big bada boom.
You're lucky you're not dead.
[Siren blares]
Officer [on loudspeaker]:
This is a police control.
Please keep your hands on the wheel.
You have an unauthorized passenger
in your vehicle.
We are going to arrest her.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Sorry, honey.
Looks like this is your ride.
Open the door.
- Akta.
- Better do what they say.
Sorry.
[♪♪♪]
[Sighs]
"Please...
Help."
I've only got one point left
on my license...
And I need that to get back to the garage
and get the cab a six-month overhaul.
You understand?
Can you please open
the passenger door?
Ple... please...
Help.
I can't.
Officer [on loudspeaker]:
I repeat...
Can you please open
your passenger door?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Why not?
Thank you for your cooperation.
Help.
Ko rb e n:
Finger's gonna kill me.
Emergency! Emergency!
Computer: One point has been
removed from your license.
Yes, I know!
On your license.
This is so stupid.
Woman [on radio]: All units assist
in pursuit of yellow cab, level 10.
Unit 47, we're on the way...
As soon as we finish lunch.
Two golden menus.
Officer 1: Thank you.
Officer 2: I'm too old, too tired...
And too hungry
to go chasing some hot rod.
Thank you so much.
And I'm definitely too thirsty.
Korben: Look out!
We got lucky.
If they don't chase you after a mile,
they don't chase you.
[♪♪♪]
[Sirens blaring]
Maybe it's two miles.
Hang on.
[Yelling in divine language]
Look, lady, I only speak two languages:
English and bad English!
Run an ID.
Don't get me wrong, I'm for conversation,
but maybe you could shut up for a minute!
I get nothing. He's got a scan blocker.
Means he's a car thief. Blast him.
I don't know what you did
to piss these guys off...
But they are really pissed off!
Hold on!
I think we're safe for a while.
You want to play it soft?
We'll play it soft.
You want to play it hard?
Let's play it hard.
[Speaking in divine language]
We make it to the fog,
we'll be all right.
If we make the fog.
How do they expect us
to find anything in this shit?
We're just gonna wait here for a little while
until things quiet down, if you don't mind.
Hey.
Shit.
You okay?
Priest.
You don't need a priest, you just
need a doctor. You'll be all right.
Vito Cornelius.
What?
Priest.
Yes?
I'm, uh, looking for a priest.
Weddings are one floor down, my son.
Congratulations.
She's not my bride. She's my fare.
She's looking for a priest
named vito Cornelius.
The phone book said he lived here.
Yes, that's me,
but I don't know who she is.
Nobody knows who she is.
No file, no ID, nothing.
She's got a tattoo on this arm here.
Tattoo?
[♪♪♪]
[Stammers]
Fifth...
Element.
Finger's gonna kill me.
- Hey! Wake up.
- Who are you?
Brought the girl, remember?
The redhead.
She just dropped in on me.
Started speaking this bizarre language.
It's not bizarre.
It's the divine language.
- The ancient language...
- Okay.
Spoken throughout the universe
before time was time. He...
He's a she.
You noticed that, huh?
Heh.
- It's a miracle.
- Miracle she's not dead.
We've not a moment to lose.
Wake her up.
But gently, because this woman is
mankind's most precious possession.
She is perfect.
[♪♪♪]
Perfect.
More dignified.
Hey, lady...
Wake up.
[Gun cocks]
You're right, I shouldn't have done that.
I shouldn't have done that.
It was wrong to kiss you.
He said to wake you gently.
You're right. You're right.
[Speaking in divine language]
Just thought you might
remember me from the cab.
Remember? "Bada boom"?
- "Big bada boom"?
- Boom?
Boom. Big bada boom.
In the cab. Here, look.
I drive a cab. This is me.
Korben Dallas.
Korben. You understand?
Here. Take it, go ahead.
You can call me
when you learn how to speak English.
Oop. Ah.
Just kidding. Kidding.
And you... what is your name?
Korben.
Leeloo minai lekarariba-laminai-tchai
ekbat de sebat.
Good. That's...
That whole thing's your name, huh?
Do you have a, uh...
A shorter name?
Not "yeah, yeah, yeah, ooh."
Shon.
[Whispers] Korben Dallas.
Leeloo.
[♪♪♪]
[In normal voice]
Korben, leeloo.
Leeloo, korben.
[Gasping]
[Laughing]
Father, are you sure
she's a supreme being?
Absolutely sure.
Old friends. Okay. Yeah, you're right.
Listen, do you think you could ask her
if I could have the gun back, please?
- What's your name?
- Korben Dallas.
Thank you, Mr. Dallas, for all your help.
Thank you so much.
You've been so kind,
but now the girl needs rest...
Because she's been on a long trip.
Yes, I know.
I was there when she landed.
Wait, wait, hey. Wait, wait, father.
She said something I didn't understand.
Well, I didn't understand any of it...
- But what does "ekto gamat" mean?
- "Never without my permission."
That's what I thought.
I shouldn't have kissed her.
[Cat meowing]
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
I forgot your food.
[Phone ringing]
How about some nice Thai food
to apologize, huh?
Yeah, yeah, hold on. What?
Finger [on phone]:
Hey, buddy, I'm waiting all day here.
- Finger.
- Where is the cab?
Car's running fine.
Purring like a kitten.
"Fine. "What "fine"?
[Know you, Dallas.
"Fine" ain't in your vocabula'y-
come on, you can tell
your old buddy finger what happened.
- What? You save the planet?
- Listen.
You dinged the Fender again. Right?
You dinged the goddamn Fender.
Finger, I was on my way over to see you
and a big fare fell in my lap.
You know, one of these really big fares
that you just can't resist.
Oh. How big?
[♪♪♪]
[Moans]
Five-nine...
Blue eyes...
Long legs, great skin.
You know. Perfect.
And this, uh, perfect fare,
she got a name?
Leeloo.
What's she doing?
Learning our history,
the last 5000 years that she's missed.
Been asleep for quite a while, you know.
[Imitating martial arts yell]
[Chuckles]
Father, I know she's been through a lot,
but we don't have much time.
Yes, you're right.
Chicken. Good.
Chicken.
I'm really sorry to interrupt you...
But the case...
With the stones...
Where is it?
[Speaking in divine language]
Who in god's name
would do such a thing?
[♪♪♪]
Excuse me, sir. The council is worried
about the economy heating up.
They wondered
if it'd be possible to fire 500,000.
Maybe from one of the smaller companies
where no one would notice...
Like one of the cab companies.
Zorg: Fire one million.
But 500,000...
One million. Fine, sir.
Sorry to have disturbed you.
[Footsteps walking]
[Footsteps running]
Oh, it's, uh...
- It's for the supreme...
- Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, sorry. Uh...
I didn't know your size, and I found you
this makeup box, okay?
- You just put it like that.
- Thank you.
Yes, there was a man with a limp...
Came here about a month ago
asking questions about the stones.
He said he was an art dealer.
[Speaking in divine language]
What was his name?
I'm so bad with names.
- They really make her...
- Perfect, I know.
[Speaking in divine language]
What did she say?
Cornelius: She says
she knows exactly where they are.
My dear aknot, how about those
two little planes that you borrowed?
Aknot, is that you? What an ugly face.
It doesn't suit you.
Take it off.
That's better.
Never be ashamed of who you are.
You're warriors. Be proud.
So what if the federal government
scattered your people to the wind.
What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger.
Your time for revenge
is at hand. Voila.
[Mangalores grunting]
It's light. Handle's adjustable for easy
carrying. Good for righties and lefties.
Breaks down into four parts,
undetectable by X-ray.
Ideal for quick, discreet interventions.
A word on firepower:
Titanium recharger, 3000-round clip
with bursts of 3 to 300.
With the replay button,
another Zorg invention, it's even easier.
And replay sends every following shot
to the same location.
[Mangalores yelling]
And to finish the job,
all the Zorg oldies but goldies.
Rocket launcher.
Arrow launcher with exploding
or poisonous gas heads.
Very practical.
Our famous net launcher.
The always-efficient flamethrower.
My favorite.
And for the grand finale,
the all-new ice-cube system.
[Mangalores applauding
and grunting]
Four full crates,
delivered right on time.
And what about you, my dear aknot?
Did you bring me what I asked you for?
Magnificent.
This case is empty.
[Laughing]
- What do you mean, empty?
- Empty...
The opposite of full.
This case is supposed to be full!
Anyone care to explain?
[Speaking in divine language]
The guardians gave the stones
to someone that they could trust.
Who took another route.
She's supposed
to contact this person...
In a hotel.
And she's looking for the address. Easy.
Dot.
[Computer beeping]
It's planet fhloston,
in the angel constellation.
- Ah. We're saved.
- I'm screwed.
You asked for a case.
We brought you a case.
A case with four stones in it!
Not one or two or three, but four!
Four stones!
What the hell am I supposed to do
with an empty case?
We are warriors, not merchants.
But you can still count!
Look, it's easy. Look at my fingers.
Four stones, four crates.
Zero stones, zero crates!
Pack everything up!
We're out of here!
[Roars]
[Guns cocking]
Aknot: We risked our lives.
I believe a little
compensation is in order.
Oh. So you are merchants after all.
Leave him one crate for the cause.
I don't like warriors.
Too narrow-minded, no subtlety...
And worse, they fight
for hopeless causes, honor.
Honor's killed millions of people.
Hasn't saved a single one.
Tell you what I do like, though: A killer.
A dyed-in-the-wool killer, cold-blooded,
clean, methodical, and thorough.
Now, a real killer,
when he picked up the zf-1
would've immediately asked about
the red button on the bottom of the gun.
[♪♪♪]
Bring me the priest.
I got everything here we need
to know about fhloston paradise...
And a detailed blueprint
of the entire hotel.
Good work, my son. Now all we've got
to do is find a way of getting there.
It's not gonna be easy. There's
a charity ball on fhloston tomorrow.
Flights are full, and with the celebrities,
the hotel will be guarded like a fortress.
But there must be a way
of getting there.
[Knocking on door]
I'll get it.
Weddings?
Not really.
- Mr. Zorg would like to talk to you.
- Mister who?
Mr. Zorg.
Zorg:
Jean-Baptiste Emmanuel Zorg.
It's nice to see you again, father.
Ah, I remember you now.
The so-called art dealer.
I'm glad you got your memory back,
because you're gonna need it.
Where are the stones?
I don't know. And even if I did know,
I wouldn't tell somebody like you.
Why?
- What's wrong with me?
- I try to serve life.
But you only...
Seem to want to destroy it.
Ah, father...
You're so wrong. Let me explain.
Life, which you so nobly serve...
Comes from destruction,
disorder and chaos.
Now, take this empty glass.
Here it is, peaceful, serene, boring.
But if it is...
Destroyed...
Look at all these little things.
So busy now.
Notice how each one is useful.
What a lovely ballet ensues,
so full of form and color.
Now, think about all those people
that created them.
Technicians, engineers.
Hundreds of people who will be able
to feed their children tonight...
So those children can grow big and
strong and have children of their own...
And so on and so forth.
Thus adding to the great chain...
Of life.
Female voice: Water. Fruit.
You see, father,
by creating a little destruction...
A cherry.
I'm, in fact, encouraging life.
In reality, you and I are
in the same business.
Cheers.
[♪♪♪]
[Choking]
Where's the robot
to pat you on the back?
Or the engineer?
[Carnival music playing]
Or their children, maybe?
You see now how all your so-called
power counts for absolutely nothing?
How your entire empire of destruction
comes crashing down...
All because of one little cherry.
[Grunting]
You saved my life...
And in return, I'll spare yours...
For now.
You're a monster, Zorg.
I know.
Torture who you have to,
the president, I don't care.
Just bring me those stones.
You have one hour.
[♪♪♪]
[Satellites beeping]
It's gobbling up all the communications
satellites in the galaxy.
Why in the hell is it eating up
all the satellites?
We're working on it, Mr. President.
I've contacted the mondoshawan.
They deplore the incident...
But they accept our apologies.
And the stones?
Did you find them in the wreckage?
- The stones weren't aboard the ship.
- What do you mean?
The mondoshawan never fully trusted
the human race.
They gave the stones
to someone they do trust.
Her name is plavalaguna.
She's a diva.
And she's going to sing at a charity ball
in fhloston paradise in a few hours.
She has the stones with her.
The mondoshawans have accepted
an offer to help.
All we have to do is send someone to get
the stones and bring them back to her.
Excellent.
[Screams]
I want this operation
to be discreet as possible.
No troops. No big operation.
I want your best man
to go undercover.
I have the perfect one.
- You got a message.
- Yeah.
Not gonna open it? Could be important.
Yeah. Like the last two I got
were important.
First one was from my wife
telling me she's leaving.
Second one was from my lawyer
telling me he was leaving with my wife.
But grandfather say:
"It never rain every day."
This is good news, guaranteed.
I bet your lunch.
Okay.
Come on.
You are fired.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Korben: Well...
[Phone ringing]
At least I won lunch.
Good philosophy.
See good in bad. I like.
- Hello.
- Woman: Korben, sweetheart.
You got broken fingers?
You can't punch my number?
- Hi, mom.
- Seventeen messages.
Don't tell me your machine is broken.
Those things are good for 1000 years.
Mr. Kim, you should go.
This is gonna take a minute.
You wouldn't even feed your pussycat,
who you obviously love more than me.
- But she didn't breast-feed you. I did.
- Goodbye, Mr. Dallas.
Ah, good fortune for you.
Up on me. Oh, Christ,
I'll never be a grandmother.
- Kim: It bring you good luck!
- Yeah, sure.
[Kim singing
in foreign language]
You know my poor body's failing me.
You have to take me on this trip.
Ma, what are you talking about?
I get it. You want to make
your only mother beg. Is that it?
No, I don't want to make you beg. All
I want is an explanation. I just got in.
I just smashed my cab.
I lost my job. I got mugged.
Besides that, everything's peachy.
Thanks for asking.
Now, will you just settle down
and explain this to me calmly?
Oh, so you don't know you won a trip
to fhloston paradise for two for 10 days.
I suppose you're just gonna leave me
on the lunar surface to freeze my ass off.
If I'd have won a trip, I'd know about it.
Somebody would've notified me.
Korben, they've been blaring your name
out on the radio for the last hour.
[Door buzzes]
Ma, I'll call you back.
General munro, how nice to see you
in the 5000 block.
Nice apartment, major.
Looks like you settled into a
wonderful life. Heard you lost your job.
You heard that, huh?
Well, don't worry. I'll get another job.
Don't bother. We have one for you.
"Major Dallas, you've been selected
for a mission of the utmost importance."
- What mission? Heh-heh-heh.
- To save the world.
"You leave immediately
for fhloston paradise.
Retrieve four stones from the diva
plavalaguna and bring them back."
- Any questions?
- Yeah, just one. Why me?
I retired six months ago,
you remember?
Three reasons.
One, as a member of the elite special
forces unit of the federated army...
You're an expert in the use of weapons
and spacecraft needed for this mission.
Two, of all the members of your unit,
you're the most highly decorated.
- And the third one?
- Of all the members of your unit...
You're the only one left alive.
You check your messages?
No, I've had enough good news
for one day.
Might be important.
Recorded voice: You're a winner!
You've won the annual gemini contest
and a trip to fhloston paradise for two.
Here are your tickets.
- You rigged the contest?
- Uh-huh.
Congratulations.
You couldn't think of anything
a little more discreet, huh?
Old tricks are the best tricks, eh?
Major iceborg will accompany you
as your wife.
I am not going.
Why not?
[♪♪♪]
[Door buzzes]
Excuse me, general.
- Who is it? Who is it?
- Huh?
- My wife.
- You remarried?
Yes. No. I just met this girl,
but I'm gonna marry her.
I love her, but she hates the military.
She knows that the military ruined
my last marriage.
She can't have anything to do with it.
If she sees you, she'll kill me.
- Major...
- Look, you gotta hide somewhere.
You gotta help me.
Just hide somewhere.
There's only one door,
where can we hide?
- Major, we don't have time for this.
- It's just for one minute.
You have no idea
how much you're helping me.
No idea... you have no idea.
- I'm going to be happily married.
- Major! Major! Major!
- What?
- The three of us won't fit in there.
- Sure you will.
- Ungh!
Munro: Major!
You're on my foot.
Major! Major!
[Speaks in divine language]
I'm really sorry to have to resort
to these methods, Mr. Wallace...
- Dallas.
We heard about your luck on the radio,
and we need your tickets for fhloston.
Is this the way
priests usually take vacations?
We're not going on vacation.
We're on a mission.
What kind of mission?
We have to save the world, my son.
[Scoffs]
- You're gonna save the world?
- Yes!
- Down there. Down there.
- Yes, sir.
[♪♪♪]
[Alarm blaring]
Male voice [on loudspeaker]:
This is a police control.
This is not an exercise.
Come on, get in.
One minute, all right?
Just stay here for one minute,
I promise.
- This is a police control.
- Don't touch anything.
This is not an exercise.
Can you please spread your legs...
And place your hands
in the yellow circles?
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna save your ass...
So you can save the world.
Yeah, but I...
I think this is the door.
There's no name and no number.
Let's see it.
Sir, are you classified as human?
Uh, negative. I am a meat Popsicle.
I found him.
Officer [on comm]:
Mr. Korben Dallas?
Sir, can you put your hands
in the yellow circles, please?
Smoke you!
Wrong answer.
[Gunshot]
Male voice [on loudspeaker]:
The police control is now terminated.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Have a nice day.
Okay, we got the guy.
Wasn't easy, but we bagged him.
- Thanks for the tip.
- Glad to be of help, my friend.
The guy's just been arrested
for uranium smuggling.
Everything's going as planned.
All I have to do now is go
to the airport, take his place...
And I'll be in fhloston
in less than four hours.
Don't come back without the stones.
[♪♪♪]
[Guns cocking]
Korben Dallas. We got him.
Perfect.
Akanit, take command.
Go to fhloston and get the stones.
If Zorg really wants them...
He'll have to negotiate.
Revenge is at hand.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I forgot about the autowash.
There's an autowash
in that shower.
I'm so sorry.
[Stammering] Autowash.
Autowash, yes.
Autowash, in the shower.
You know, it's funny.
I've met you twice today.
Both times,
you've ended up in my arms.
It's my lucky day.
[Shivering] Lucky day.
[Groaning]
Did you hear something?
Cornelius.
Korben: Oh!
[Gasps]
Autowash.
- I'm so sorry. Sorry.
- I don't need your help.
- Want a cup of coffee?
- Yes, please.
Leeloo: Autowash.
Coffee's not really my specialty.
But you must drink a lot of coffee,
being a priest, huh?
[Grunts]
No, I know. I'm not proud of what I did.
I had no choice.
[♪♪♪]
[Groans]
I'll take the mission.
[♪♪♪]
[Woman speaking indistinctly
on loudspeaker]
- Did you get them?
- Yeah, I got them.
- "Leeloo Dallas."
- "Multi-pass."
"Korben David Dallas." Perfect.
[Speaking in divine language]
No, no. I can't possibly be
your husband. I'm too old.
Now, David is...
In great shape. He'll protect you.
Now, please, go to the diva, collect
the stones and meet me at the temple.
Now. Yes?
Okay.
Woman [on loudspeaker]:
Final call for fhloston paradise.
Last call for fhloston paradise.
Hurry up.
[Stammering] The tickets.
- ID, please.
- I'm sorry. Uh...
- There.
- In here?
Female voice: Thank you!
Mr. Dallas?
Congratulations on winning the contest.
Oh, right. Okay.
- Sorry for the mess.
- The mess?
The garbage.
Oh, right... it's k...
[Speaks in divine language]
I was so afraid
I wasn't gonna make this flight...
So I sent David here to come
and pick up my boarding pass.
- But, um...
- But now David has to go.
Thank you. Bye.
I am korben Dallas.
Woman [on loudspeaker]:
Please report infractions to the spaceport.
And, uh, this is?
Leeloo Dallas. Multi-pass.
- Yeah. Lee... multi-pass.
- Multi-pass.
She knows it's a multi-pass.
Leeloo Dallas.
My wife. We're newlyweds.
Just met. You know how it is.
Bump into each other, sparks happen...
Yeah, she knows it's a multi-pass.
Yeah. Anyway, we're in love.
I mean,
I know she's made to be strong.
She's also so fragile, so human.
Know what I mean?
- Robot: Do you want some more?
- Yeah.
Make that two.
Oh, David. David?
- Where's leeloo?
- She's on the plane with Mr. Dallas.
- What?!
- I'm sorry, father.
I didn't know what to do.
I thought he was gonna kill me.
But this is not possible.
This is not possible.
Robot: You want some more?
This is all my fault. It's...
I am the servant. It is my mission.
I shouldn't have given it to you.
I know.
- Here's the key to the temple.
- Oh, no.
Prepare for our arrival.
I go to face my destiny. Yes.
I don't want to go to Egypt.
Female voice: Thank you!
Dallas? Korben Dallas?
Yeah, that's me.
Um... just a minute, please.
Heh. It will take just one more minute.
[Grumbung]
We'll be right back.
Oh, Mr. Dallas.
Oh, um, we really need you right now.
Ruby rhod is broadcasting live
and he needs you for an interview.
Multi-pass.
Tell aknot that plan a flopped.
Go to plan b.
Aliens ahead. Spread out.
[Crowd screaming]
Backup unit, zone 18.
Mr. Ruby rhod is the biggest radio star,
you know.
It's a great honor to be on his talk show.
- He's so green.
- Yes, I'm sure you're very excited.
But I'm on my vacation
and I don't want to be bothered.
I prefer to remain anonymous.
[Fan fare playing]
Korben Dallas!
Here he is! The one and only winner
of the gemini croquette contest.
This boy is fueled like fire,
so start melting, ladies...
Because the boy is hotter than hot.
He's hot, hot, hot!
[Electronic music playing]
The right size, the right build,
the right hair, the right on.
Male voice: Right on.
Right on, right on.
And he's got something to say...
To those 50 billion pairs
of ears out there.
Pop it, d-man.
Uh, hi.
Unbelievable.
[Dance music playing]
Quiver, ladies, quiver.
He's gonna set the world on fire.
Right here from 5 to 7.
You'll know everything
there is to know about the d-man.
His dreams...
His desires...
His most intimates of intimates.
And from what I'm looking at, intimate
is this studmuffin's middle name.
- So tell me, my man...
- Woman: Aah!
You nervous in the service?
Uh, not really.
Freeze those knees because korben's
in the place and he's on the case.
Yesterday's frog
will be tomorrow's prince...
Of fhloston paradise!
The hotel of a thousand and one follies,
lollies and lick-them-lollies.
A magic fountain flow
of non-stop wine, women...
And hootchie-kootchie-koo...
All night long.
♪ all night long all night ♪♪
[sound of wolf howling]
Start licking your
stamps, little girlies...
Because this guy's gonna
have you writing home to mama.
Right, here, from 5 to 7,
I'll be your voice, your tongue...
And I'll be hot on the trail
of the sexiest man of the year:
D-man, your man...
[Panting]
My man.
[Moans]
Man [on radio]:
End of transmission.
Woman [on radio]:
Okay, Ruby. See you tomorrow at 5.
How was it?
- Oh! Wow.
- Oh!
- It was just absolutely green.
- I was touched to the core.
Green like what?
- Oh.
- Crystal green.
Any kind of green you want...
Tree green, emerald, pond green.
[Buzzing]
Korben, sweetheart, what was that?
It was bad! It had nothing!
No fire! No energy! No nothing! You know
I have a show to run here. You know?
And it must pop, pop, pop!
So tomorrow, from 5 to 7...
Will you please act like you have
more than a two-word vocabulary?
It must be green! Okay? Okay?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Can I just talk to you?
I didn't come here
to play pumba on the radio.
So tomorrow, from 5 to 7,
you're gonna give yourself a hand.
- Green?
- Super-green.
Dallas? Korben Dallas?
That's me. Ha-ha-ha.
I only have one korben Dallas on my list,
and he's already checked in, okay?
That's impossible.
I am korben Dallas.
- Sorry, sir. Boarding is finished.
- Hey.
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, hey, hey!
I need to talk to someone!
I don't believe this!
Male voice [on loudspeaker]:
This is a police control.
- Okay, I'm sorry. I'm calm.
- Put your hands in the yellow circles.
There's been a mistake.
To make your flight
as short as possible...
Our flight attendants are switching
on the sleep regulator...
Which will regulate your sleeping
during the flight.
Thank you.
- Oh, you speak English now.
- Yes. I learn.
Leeloo, we are not on vacation.
I'm on a very important mission.
I work for some very important people.
If I hadn't come to get you, you would be
in big trouble. Do you understand that?
- Do you understand? Big trouble?
- Yes.
But you, no trouble.
Me, fifth element.
Supreme being.
Me protect you.
Sleep.
[♪♪♪]
- Sweet dreams, Mr. Dallas.
- No, wait...
Sleep regulator operative
in zone one, captain.
Thank you.
Zone two, are you operative?
Zone two?
Yeah, everything's ready, captain.
- Mr. Rhod.
- What?
You're gonna have to assume
your individual position.
I don't want one position,
I want all positions!
[Buzzing]
- Parasites in landing gear.
- Ground, you copy?
Got it. Front gear.
Hey, man, give me some heat, man!
We need some heat here, man!
Give me some heat!
Some heat over here, man!
Good shit, man.
Put the heat over here, man!
[Parasites squealing]
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Come, come, come.
Give me this. Give me this.
You can call me Ruby.
Fueled and ready to go.
- Yep. All right.
- I'll buy you one, man.
Zorg:
Have you taken off already?
- I'm not on the plane.
- What?
The real Dallas took my place.
I don't understand.
Are you making fun of me?
No, no, no! I swear! I swear!
I never felt this way before
with a human.
- Really?
- Yeah!
I've tried everything, sir. There's
no other way of getting on this plane.
[Engine whirring]
- Ground is clear.
- Roger. Ready for liftoff?
Copilot: Confirmed.
Not there. No, please, not there.
Please, not there.
- Power pressure?
- Primed.
- Protection?
- Confirmed.
Pilot: Power increase.
Ten seconds.
A little...
- Disappointed.
- Five.
And if there is one thing I do not like...
- Three...
- It is to be...
- Disappointed.
- One.
Sorry, sir.
This will never happen again.
- I know.
- Liftoff.
[Screaming]
- Landing gear secure.
- Roger. Checklist for light speed.
[♪♪♪]
[Pinging]
Sir, we're finally getting something.
It's sending radio wavelengths.
- What does it want with radio waves?
- Maybe it wants to make a call.
[Phone ring/ng]
Zorg's office.
[Comm beeps]
I told you,
I do not want to be disturbed.
I know you don't want to be disturbed
except if it's Mr. Shadow...
And it's Mr. Shadow on the line.
[♪♪♪]
Shadow: It's shadow again.
Zorg here.
- Am I disturbing you?
- No, no, no, I was just...
Where are you?
Shadow: Not far now.
Good, good.
How are the stones?
Fine. Fine. Just fine.
I'll have the, uh...
I'll have the four stones
that you asked for any time now...
But it wasn't easy.
My costs have tripled.
Money is of no importance.
I want the stones.
The stones...
Will be here.
I'll see to it personally.
I will be among you...
- We lost it.
- We lost the signal.
Damn!
[Pants]
Female voice [on loudspeaker]:
We've begun our descent.
The local time is 3:20 P.M.
Auto-temperature is
currently 85 degrees fahrenheit.
We do hope you've enjoyed your flight
and hope to see you again soon.
[Airship horn blaring]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Spaceship docks]
Man [on loudspeaker]:
Ladies and gentlemen...
Welcome to paradise.
[All cheering]
[Band playing island music]
[Singing in foreign language]
Excuse me, dear. Excuse me.
Thank you. Excuse me, please.
[Speaking indistinctly]
[Buzzing]
Parasites in main ventilation.
Again? Don't worry, I'll get it.
[Yells]
- Have we arrived yet?
- Yeah.
Oh, good.
We have 12 swimming pools
and two on the rooftop.
All the restaurants are
between level 2 and level 10.
The planet fhloston has 400 beaches,
all accessible until 5 P.M.
Then the airship goes higher to offer you
a better view with your dinner.
- Is the diva here yet?
- Not yet.
Are there any tickets left for this opera?
I'm a really big fan.
You have a seat reserved, front row...
Next to Ruby rhod!
He's so talented, don't you think?
I just love him. He's so sexy.
Anyway, he has your ticket for the show,
and he'll be here in 20 minutes.
Do you know
where I can get something to wear?
- Enjoy your evening, Mr. Dallas.
- Thank you.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Mrs. Dallas [on phone]:
I never should've pushed you out.
- Ma?
- I was in labor for days...
And this is how you repay me?
- I should've just gotten a robot.
- Come on, ma.
Don't "come on, ma" me.
I should be there, not you.
- I need a tan. I need a cocktail.
- Ma...
[M]
[Speaks indistinctly]
[Whispering] Get the case in.
[In normal voice]
Hello, Ms. Diva. I'm fog.
Welcome to the... I am, uh, security.
Welcome to the... tall...
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Sure. Yeah.
- What's your name?
- Uh, fog.
Ms. Plavalaguna wants you to know
how glad she is that you're here.
She'll give you what you've come
to get after the concert.
Stay here.
Man [on radio]: You're listening
to radio cosmos, and it is now 5 P.M.
- Helm to 108.
- Yes, sir.
Man [on radio]: Time to join
Ruby rhod and korben Dallas...
The lucky winner
of the gemini croquette contest.
Coming at you live from fhloston...
Paradise!
[Electronic music playing]
Ruby rhod at your service for two hours
with korben and the hotel manager...
And miss gemini croquette in person...
And 8000 other lucksters here...
To enjoy the privilege of the unique
concert of miss plavalaguna!
[Buzzing]
And now we enter what must be...
The most beautiful concert hall
in all the universe!
A perfect replica
of the old opera house...
But who cares?
To my right, a row of ministers,
more sinisters than ministers.
To my left, baby ray,
star of stage and screen.
He's not gonna get much out
of this concert, because he's stone-deaf!
To who?
And here we have Roy Von baker,
king of laser ball.
And here, the emperor of kodar japhet
and his lovely daughter.
"I love to sing,"
she recently confessed to me.
By the way, I have a recording
of her talented voice.
[Sound of woman moaning plays]
I'll play you the rest of the song
after the concert, because right now...
It's time for korben to say
the word of the day.
So tell me, my man,
you happy here in the big world?
And now champagne!
Commercial! Commercial!
Man [on earpiece]:
Break for 30 seconds.
[Buzzing]
[Sighs]
[Growling]
[Classical music playing]
[Singing inva mulla tchako's
Aria of "Lucia di lammermoor"]
Commander, I have a ship in trouble
requesting permission to clock for repairs.
Put him in the docking garage.
- Inform security.
- Sir.
Man [on radio]:
Permission granted for one hour.
More than I need.
[Knocking on door]
Yes?
Man: Champagne for the diva.
[Gunshot]
[Speaking in foreign language]
[Panting]
I found it.
[M]
[Dance music playing]
Get her!
[Singing inva mulla tchako's
"the diva dance"]
Huh?
[Grunting]
[Gun clicks]
[Music ends]
[All cheering]
It was an ambush.
[Growling]
If it's war they want,
it's war they'll get!
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo! Bravo.
My compliments, little lady.
Thank you for doing all the dirty work.
I couldn't have done a betterjob myself.
Hand over the stones.
[Gun cocks]
Nobody move!
We're taking over the ship!
Hands up!
[Audience screaming]
Ruby! Ruby!
[Screaming]
[Gunfire]
[Crowd screaming]
I know this music.
Let's change the beat.
[Ticking]
Something's happening here.
I think we're being attacked.
I don't know who they are,
but they're everywhere. Wait.
I see one of them.
They're warriors, and they're ugly.
They got big teeth and they got big
foreheads and big ears, and they stink.
Mangalores.
[M]
Korben: The government sent me
to help you. Just stay calm.
If somebody hears this,
come and get me. I'm in the first row.
[Growling]
- You must give her the stones.
- Who?
The fifth element.
The supreme being sent to earth
to save the universe.
- Leeloo?
- Yes.
But she's more fragile
than she seems.
She needs your help...
And your love...
Or she will die.
[Groaning]
- No, no, no. Stay with me.
- Help!
[Crying]
If you want something done,
do it yourself. Yep!
Come on, honey. You can't die.
Come on. Listen to me. Wake up!
- Where are the stones?
- What?
The stones. Where are the stones?
The stones.
[Laughing]
[Crying]
They're not here.
The stones, where are they?
In me.
What? What?
Oh, my god, korben.
Korben, another one coming.
Korben. Korben, I think we should go.
One minute. Just give me a minute.
Mangalore: Hey, you!
I said, you.
- I'm not with him.
- Where's the other?
[Ruby screams]
[Gun cocks]
I said, one minute. Ruby, hold this gun.
- What? What do you want me to do?
- Hold this gun.
- Come on. Put your hand on it.
- Oh, my god.
- Got it? Hold it.
- What do I do?
If he moves, squeeze the trigger.
I don't feel right.
I don't feel right, korben.
The stones are "in me."
Korben, I got a headache. This ain't me.
[Gunshot]
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Think he's gonna be okay?
[Growling]
Oh, my god. Oh, my god, korben.
Another one coming.
Aw, shit. Three coming, korben. Three.
[Screams]
Listen, you guard this with your life...
Or you're gonna look like
this guy right here. You green?
-Green. Korben: Super-green?
- Ruby: Super-green.
- Is that your idea...
Of a discreet operation?
Don't worry, sir. I know my man.
He'll calm things down.
[Gunfire]
All right.
[Yelling]
Move! Move!
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is amazing.
- Let me do it.
- Right.
Oh, my god. Korben Dallas, korben,
my man. Korben Dallas is in trouble.
Hey. Ray!
The gun!
Give me the gun. The gun. The gun!
I'm gonna go and try to see
if I can see something a little closer.
Yes, the gun. Yeah.
Thanks, ray.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Don't shoot! I'm not armed!
Gmum
you've got the wrong guy! Don't shoot!
I'm not armed! I'm not armed!
[Growls]
Oh, my god.
Korben: I'm on vacation.
It's... don't shoot me, please.
I'm on a vacation. I won a...
Contest.
Gemini croquette's to fhloston paradise.
Down.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- Get down!
[M]
I think he's trying
to say something to me.
- Get down!
- Okay.
[Screams]
[Gunfire]
Sorry. Sorry, my man.
Korben. Korben?
Where are you, man?
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Korben.
They're coming.
Korben, they're coming.
[Ruby crying]
Korben!
- Don't move.
- What?
[Screams]
- What you doing?
- Count to 10.
- Korben? Was that a bomb?
- Just shut up and count!
One, two, three, four, five...
Six, seven, eight...
Nine...
[Ruby screaming]
[Ruby panting]
[Screams]
[Ticking]
I am very disappointed!
Korben, my man.
Korben, what are you looking for?
Control room.
- This is it.
- I'll be over here, all right?
Let's go! Let's go!
Quiet! Quiet!
- You in charge?
- Yeah.
How many of them are out there?
- I don't know.
- Let's count.
[Mangalores growling]
Seven on the left. Five on the right.
[Gunfire]
Four on the right. Two on the left.
We need to find the leader.
Mangalores won't fight without the leader.
One more shot
and we start killing hostages.
- That's the leader.
- Send someone to negotiate.
[Stammering]
I've never negotiated.
You mind if I try?
No, no. Sure, sure. Sure.
We're sending somebody in
to negotiate!
[Gunshot]
Anybody else wanna negotiate?
Where did he learn
to negotiate like that?
I wonder.
Where's Ruby?
I thought he was dead.
Master!
It was nothing, really.
It was just a helping hand.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Ruby rhod...
Still alive. Aah!
What's wrong with you? It hurt!
Wow. Zoom.
[Cornelius chuckles]
Korben, I realize
that you must be pretty mad at me...
But I want you to know
that I am fighting for a noble cause.
Yes, you're trying to save the world.
I remember.
Right now I'm trying
to save leeloo, father.
- Leeloo's in trouble?
- When is leeloo not in trouble?
- There. Where is that?
- Man: That's the diva's suite.
Leeloo.
[M]
Leeloo. Hang on.
Here, come on. How the hell do you
get yourself into these positions?
Come on.
Yeah, I'm here. It's all right.
It's all right. Everything's okay now.
Listen.
[Ticking]
I got the stones.
All right, just take it easy, all right?
[Whimpers]
My man, my man, my man.
What's this thing with all these numbers?
[M]
No, no, no.
Because if it was a bomb...
The alarms would go off because all
these hotels have bomb detectors. Right?
[Alarm buzzing]
Female voice [on loudspeaker]:
This is a type a alert.
For security reasons,
the hotel must be evacuated.
Please proceed calmly
to the lifeboats...
Stay calm!
Located in the main hallways.
Please, stay calm!
[All screaming]
Stay calm.
Korben. Korben, my man,
you know how to stop this, right?
Korben?
Female voice [on loudspeaker]:
Two minutes to complete evacuation.
- Get back!
- Evacuation! Evacuation!
Sorry, sir, you can't stay here.
There's a bomb in the hotel.
I know.
[All screaming]
- Ruby: I don't want to die.
- Please, my son.
Get in. Get in.
Female voice [on loudspeaker]:
One minute to total evacuation.
This one.
Forty-five seconds.
Korben: Get her strapped in.
Korben, korben. Korben, my man,
you know how to fly this thing?
Just like driving a cab.
[Engine whirring]
But the door?
How we gonna get out the door?
Fifteen seconds.
Ten, nine, eight...
Seven, six, five...
[Exhales]
[Grunts]
[Beeping]
For the honor.
[Ticking]
Oh, no.
- You should hold on.
- Aah!
Come on.
[Exhales]
Like driving a cab.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is now 7 P.M. time for the news.
See you tomorrow
for a new adventure.
Man [on earpiece]:
End of transmission.
That's the best show I ever did.
[Exhales]
Mr. President, major Dallas has
the five elements on board...
And the priest is guiding them
directly to the temple.
[M]
We're saved.
[Snoring]
The diva said
that I should take care of you.
Humans act so strange.
What do you mean?
Everything you create...
Is used to destroy.
We call it human nature.
You learn about that on your screen?
I'm not finished yet. I'm up to v.
V is good.
Some very good words in v.
Like what?
Valiant.
Vulnerable.
Very beautiful.
[All cheering]
President: Oh, of course, munro!
- Mr. President?
- Yes, now what?
We have a problem.
What do you mean, it's advancing?
It's moving at incredible speed.
We're having trouble following it.
And do you have any idea
where it's heading?
Korben, there's a general
on the, urn, phone.
I'll give you to the president.
Major Dallas, I first would like
to salute a warrior.
You're a shining example
of this army's might.
- Mr. President.
- In the name of the federation...
Any idea when you're
gonna be getting to the point?
[Sighs]
Okay. There's a ball of fire 1200 miles
in diameter heading straight for earth...
And we have no idea how to stop it.
That's the problem.
[Sighs]
How much time do we have?
If its speed remains constant,
in an hour and 57 minutes.
I'll call you back in two hours.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
[M]
They just landed in the desert.
Cornelius: Good job, David.
- Put her in the center.
- Where? Here?
You got it figured out, father?
This one should be fire.
- You know how all this works?
- Theoretically, yes.
- Theoretically?
- The four stones should go around.
The fifth element should be
in the middle...
And then the weapon
against evil should work.
You've never seen this work before,
have you?
Every weapon has a manual.
I'm sure this has one too.
That's it. That's it.
Match up the symbols. Go! Go!
My man, what you doing?
- What?
- What you doing?
Trying to keep you in the dj business.
Fire.
Done.
- So, what happens now?
- So now we have to open them.
- And you know how to do that, right?
- Theoretically...
Leeloo, wake up, honey, wake up.
You have to help us.
Leeloo. How do you open these stones?
Fire burns.
Yes, I know all that.
But how do you open these stones?
Rain...
Falls.
Korben [softly]: What?
Leeloo. Leeloo.
What does it mean?
I think that, um...
- Maybe it's a charade.
- What?
A game or something.
If we don't get these stones open
in five minutes, we're all dead.
- Dead?
- Yes, dead.
[M]
Too late.
- We've lost contact with them.
- Three minutes.
I think mine is broken.
Why I gotta get the broke one?
We're never gonna make it.
[Sighs]
Korben. Korben, it moved!
What'd you do?
Show me what you did.
- Nothing.
- Shut up, shut up!
Calm down. Show me what you did.
Take me through it, step by step.
- I was just standing here like this.
- Quickly.
Okay, and I put my hands
on the top like this, and I said:
"We're not gonna make it."
That's it?
[Sighs]
Ruby: Korben, my man.
She said, "wind... wind blows."
[Blowing]
Everyone take a stone.
Water for water. Fire for fire.
Earth for earth. Go, now!
- Open the other one.
- Okay.
K... korben.
Korben, my man, I have no fire.
I have no matches.
Do you have any matches?
I stopped smoking. If I knew...
I mean... father, you smoke?
Got some matches? Matches?
We need some fire.
We all gonna die.
[Sighs]
Don't breathe.
[All gasp]
[Ruby whimpers]
Fire.
One minute.
Korben:
Let's go. Let's go. Leeloo.
Wake up. Wake up.
It's time for you to work now.
Protect life...
Until death.
No, no, leeloo! Listen to me!
Listen to me. Listen.
Listen, I know you're very tired.
I know you're very tired.
I'll take you on a vacation when
we're done. I swear, just you and me.
But if you don't do something right now,
we're all gonna die. You understand?
What's the use of saving life
when you see what you do with it?
It'll be entering the atmosphere
in 40 seconds.
Korben: Leeloo, you're right.
But there are some things...
Very nice things worth saving,
some beautiful things.
Beautiful things.
Like love?
Yes, love. That's good. That's good.
That's a good example.
Like love. Love is worth saving.
I don't know love.
I was built to protect, not to love.
So there's no use for me
other than this.
No, no, no, you're wrong.
You're wrong. You're wrong.
I need you. I need you very much.
Why?
Because"_
Tell her, korben.
Tell me. Please.
Why do you need me?
- Because...
- Tell me.
- Because I...
Because I love you.
[Whispers] I love you.
[Sobbing]
[M]
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
Six, five, four, three...
Two, one.
[Yelling]
[Thunder rumbling]
[M]
Man [on radio]: Scanner imaging
has confirmed the dark planet: Dead.
The planet seems to have stopped
at 62 miles from impact.
[Chuckles]
What's wrong with you?
What you screaming for?
Every five minutes, it's something.
A bomb or something.
I'm leaving. Bzz!
[Sirens blaring]
[President laughing]
Let me introduce you to professor
mactilburgh who runs the center.
It's an honor to receive you,
Mr. President.
Yes, well...
Where are my two heroes?
Oh, they were so tired from their ordeal,
we put them in the reactor this morning.
I have 19 more meetings after this one.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Let me see if they're revived.
Thank you.
We go live in one minute,
Mr. President.
[Gasps]
They're...
Not ready.
Uh, they need...
- Five more minutes.
- You have 20 seconds.
No, ma'am.
No, no, I tried. No, ma'am.
Who's that?
Some woman.
Claims to be korben's mother.
Well, give it here.
Mrs. Dallas, this is the president.
On behalf of the federation...
Mrs. Dallas:
Please, that doesn't even sound like him.
The president's an idiot.
You don't sound like an idiot.
If you don't want to talk to your mother,
just avoid me like usual.
I 7! Just throw myself in traffic.
I'll just saran wrap myself to the bed...
[Mrs. Dallas speaking
indistinctly]
[R.x.r.a.'s "the little light
of love" playing]
♪ rely on your light ♪
♪ on your inner loving powerj'
♪ a little light as sole religion ♪
♪ we will lead a light of love ♪
♪ a little light of love and freedom ♪
♪ a little light as sole religion ♪
♪ we will lead a light of love ♪
♪ a little light will solve our freedom ♪
♪ just a little light of love ♪
♪ a little light as sole religion ♪
♪ take this little light of love ♪
♪ a little light of love and freedom ♪
♪ a little light as sole religion ♪
♪ a little light ♪
♪ a little light of love and freedom ♪
♪ a little light as sole religion ♪
♪ a little light, a little light ♪
♪ a little light of love and freedom ♪
♪ a little light as sole religion ♪
♪ a little light of love and freedom ♪♪